我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
But secretly, with the help
我秘密地打击犯罪
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但是我在时间中迷失了
But I became lost in time.
我的朋友们用尽了一切办法
It took everything in my friends' power
才把我救回来  但我们的世界
to bring me back, and in doing so
也因此出现了新的威胁
our world was opened up to new threats.
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
他的眼泪不只是水
His tears are more than just water.
像是春药
It's like a love drug.
我好像会读心术
I think I can read minds.
塞西尔有心灵感应能力
Cecile's a telepath.
比起把艾伦从监狱里救出来
That's way more important
这件事更重要
than getting Allen out of prison.
上周塞西尔已经提出了上诉
Cecile filed an appeal last week.
我们没有新证据  所以那不重要
We have no new evidence, so that doesn't matter.
你知道这一区不是只有一个
Did you know the oscillating cameras
来回摆动的摄像头吧
aren't the only ones in this wing?
你就是闪电侠
You're The Flash.
你说我准备好做交易时就打给你
You said to call you when I was ready to do business.
你还有别的鱼卖我吗
Do you have another fish to sell me?
上锁
解锁成功
欢迎来到我私人的超能力者关押区
Welcome to my own personal meta-block,
以第一代铁山监狱的废墟为基础建立的
built on the ruins of the first Iron Heights--
完全是黑市  而且是监控探头的盲区
completely off the books and camera-free.
好了  少说点历史  多逛逛
Yes, yes, less history lesson, more window shopping.
米娜·沙伊唐
Mina Chaytan--
她的超能力是把赋予雕像生命
her powers bring effigies to life.
那真是超赞的伎俩
Now, that is a nifty trick.
她还能把其他什么变活吗
Can she animate anything else, hm?
我的手指怎么样
How about my finger?
我喜欢她  脾气很臭
Oh, I like her, she's feisty.
那你肯定会爱上我
You are going to love me,
而且我自愿跟你走  美女
and I'll come willingly, gorgeous.
希尔伯特·伦丁  他可以把物体压缩
Sylbert Rundine-- he can shrink objects
也可以让他们变回原来大小
and return them to original size.
我认识一个毒贩会为那家伙
I know a drug smuggler who'd pay
付大价钱
a pretty pence for that man.
拉姆齐·迪肯  控制科技
Ramsey Deacon-- controls technology.
还有贝琪·夏普
And Becky Sharpe--
可以在量子级操控运气
can manipulate luck on the quantum level.
我闻到了投标战的味道
I smell a bidding war.
这会是谁呢
And who might this be?
一个你等待了很久的人
Something you've been wanting for a long time--
一个极速者
a speedster.
主菜来了
C'est piece de resistance.
条件和以前一样
Terms are the same as always.
你卖出任何超能力者  我们利润对半
Any metas you sell, we split the profits evenly.
所以  你要哪个
So, who would you like?
剪刀  石头
eenie, meenie,
布
miney,
他们所有人
all of them.
闪 电 侠
第四季
第十三集
黑色达卡
Drakkar Noir,
洋葱
onions,
肝泥香肠
and liverwurst?
不
Oh, no.
厄尔·考克斯
Earl Cox.
厄尔
Earl!
警察来了
It's the cops.
不是我
It wasn't me!
我要和你们每个人战斗  呼哈
I'll fight every one of you, ha-ya, ha-ya!
好啊  拉尔夫
Oh, hello, Ralphy.
你怎么进来的  厄尔
How'd you get in here, Earl?
门没锁
Door was unlocked.
门锁了
No, it wasn't.
我撬开之后是没锁
Was after I picked it.
看看你
Look at you.
你在我面前简直是扎克·埃夫隆
You went all Zac Efron on me.
美国男演员
多喝点酒  你的6块腹肌就会变1块了
You drank so many six packs you'd have grown one.
西服不错  厄尔
Nice suit, Earl.
谢谢你好意
Ah, thank you kindly--
阿玛尼的仿品  我超爱
Armani knockoff, I love it.
听着  我能见到你很高兴
Listen, it's always great seeing you,
但请原谅  我今天很忙
but if you'll excuse me, I got a very busy day.
清空你今天的日程  瘦子
Clear your calendar, slim,
因为我有个大单  能让你
'cause I've got a score that'll
在下一个圣诞节吃上蜜汁火腿
knock your honey glazed holiday ham into next Christmas.
我觉得没什么词语
Yeah, I don't think any of those words
能形容明白你的意思
mean what you think they do.
这几个词怎么样
How about these words for you?
一个富二代老女人雇我找他另一个男朋友
A rich, old heiress hires me to find her other boyfriend,
那个可怜男孩  就是个骗女人钱的
the pool boy, as a gold digger.
他就是这样的人
Turns out, he is.
但是这可怜男孩愿意把钱
But pool boy is willing to share said gold
分享给一个愿意帮他假装一切正常的人
with someone who can help him keep up appearances,
也就是说  我的朋友
so to speak, and that, my friend,
这是你的专长
is your specialty.
入伙不
Are you in?
我再也不做这种事了
I don't do that kind of stuff anymore.
拉尔夫·德比得专心
Ralph Dibny needs to concentrate.
-看到了吗  -我现在有朋友了
- You see this? - I got friends now.
他们都是好人
They're good people.
他们帮助我
They helped me, uh,
翻开了新的一页
turn over a new leaf.
-是吗  -是的
- Are they, now? - Yeah.
走着瞧吧
We'll see.
什么意思
Meaning?
意思就是
Meaning,
我喜欢你  拉尔夫  真的
I love you, Ralphy, I really do.
但你总是让人失望
But you let people down,
尤其是让那些好人失望
especially the good ones.
他们和你很亲近  信任你
They get close to you, place their trust in you,
然后  彭
and then, bam,
你搞砸了
you screw up,
每一次
every single time.
当你让你新朋友失望的时候
So, when you let your new friends down,
给你老朋友打个电话
give your old one a call.
谢谢你来  塞西尔
Thanks for coming, Cecile.
我知道巴里对于
I know Barry isn't too optimistic
这次上诉听证会并不乐观
about the appeal hearing.
别丢掉希望  爱瑞丝
Don't lose hope, Iris,
我们还有几天可以准备
we still have a few days to prepare.
我知道  但我们又没有
I know, but it's not like
想出什么新主意
we've come up with any new ideas
为巴里正名
for clearing Barry's name.
更大的问题是  巴里好像不在
A bigger issue is we don't seem to have Barry.
-韦斯特·艾伦女士吗 -沃夫监狱长
- Mrs. West-Allen? - Warden Wolfe.
不幸的是  你可能今天看不到你丈夫来了
Unfortunately, you won't be able to see your husband today.
他卷入了一场争斗
He was in an altercation.
什么  争斗
What-- an altercation?
监狱里的群架
A prison yard fight.
什么  他还好吗
What? Is he okay?
他没事  没事
Oh, he's fine, he's fine,
他没受伤  也不是他的错
he wasn't harmed and he wasn't at fault,
但依据铁山监狱的规章
but per Iron Heights protocol,
每个卷入争端的人都要禁闭一周
everyone involved is in isolation for the week.
那他会安全吗
And is he safe there?
他不可能再安全了
Oh, he couldn't be more safe.
实际上  这种事件经常发生
Actually, it's a pretty common occurrence.
午夜前是安全的
Safe until midnight...
然后艾伦和其他人就归阿姆内特了
and then Allen and the others belong to Amunet.
重要的是  他会受到很好的照料
The important thing to know is, he's in good hands.
你晚上可以睡个好觉
You can rest easy at night.
谢谢你  典狱长
Thank you, Warden.
是  谢谢你
Yes, thank you.
怎么了
What's wrong?
沃夫在拐卖超能力者吗
Wolfe is trafficking meta-humans?
这城市里的人都是腐败的吗
Is everybody crooked in this town?
他穿着那身意式羊毛西装总看着很体面
Ah, he always did look smug in those Italian wool suits.
天啊  他完美诠释了披着羊皮的狼
Oh, my God, he's literally wolf in sheep's clothing.
这真是完美的一对合作伙伴
It's kind of the perfect partnership, I mean,
阿姆内特买卖超能力者
Amunet deals in metas,
沃夫有一监狱这样的人
and Wolfe has a prison full of them.
而且他是典狱长
And him being the Warden,
他可以神不知鬼不觉
he can make some inmates disappear
就让一些罪犯消失
without raising any eyebrows.
我要去和辛格谈谈
I'm gonna go talk to Singh.
说什么
And say what?
你怀孕的女朋友
Your pregnant girlfriend
用她孕期的通灵能力告诉你的
with gestational psychic powers told you?
是的  乔  辛格只会觉得
Yeah, Joe, Singh's just gonna think that
你是一个急于把儿子救出监狱的父亲
you're a father desperate to get his son out of prison.
如果我们在午夜前弄不清原委
Well, if we don't figure out something before midnight,
我就准备这么说
that's exactly what I'm gonna say.
哈里人呢  他能帮忙的
Hey, where's Harry? He can help.
他去地球二了  去看看杰西  所以
He went to Earth Two, he's checking in on Jesse, so...
-太好了  -好吧  我们没有合法的选择了
- Great. - Okay, well, we're out of legal options,
西斯科也没法打开缺口让巴里从超能力者监狱逃出
and Cisco can't breach Barry out of the meta-wing,
我们怎么阻止这一切
so, how do we stop this?
收到你们的通知了  很抱歉我迟到了
Hey, guys, got your alert, sorry I'm late.
-没什么大不了的  拉尔夫  -才不是
- It's okay, Ralph. - No, it's not okay.
我碰到了一个过去的生意伙伴
I ran into this old business partner of mine.
这家伙就是个又大又肥的变态
This guy-- he's just a big, fat creep.
他老是多管我的闲事
He's always sticking his nose in my business.
天哪
Oh, my.
他还特别阴险
And he's so shady.
他长着一双豆豆眼  总笑得很邪恶
He's got these beady eyes and this crooked smile.
一个彻头彻尾的双面派鼠辈
Just a real two-faced rat from head to toe.
真吓人
Well... Freaky.
什么
What?
他就是个两面派小人
He's a two-faced rat, he is.
我声音怎么了
What's wrong with my voice?
你们听到了吗
Do you hear that?
那就是他  就在这里
That's him right there.
那就是他  你们看到他了吗  那就是他
That's him, do you see him? That's him.
那是他  是他  是他
That's him, that's him, that's him,
就在这  他就在
Right there, there he...
在
there...
那是我  那是我
That's me, that's me.
这是怎么回事
What is happening?
你不知怎么把自己
You somehow willed your body
变成了厄尔的样子
to shape shift into Earl's appearance.
看起来你的细胞不止是会伸缩啊
Seems like your cells can do a lot more than just elongate.
真棒  这个怎么撤销啊
Ugh, brilliant. How do you undo it?
撤销这个  那个  这个
Undo this? That? This?
[电脑快捷键  经常用于撤销上一步操作]
控制键加Z
Control Z?
控制...
Control...
各位  我刚想到了阻止沃夫监狱长的法子
Guys, I think I just figured out how to stop Warden Wolfe.
如果拉尔夫可以变成那个《勇敢的心》
If Ralph could shape shift into Braveheart here,
《勇敢的心》主角为苏格兰人  厄尔也是苏格兰人
那他也很容易变成沃夫
then he could easily shape shift into Wolfe
然后在午夜前见阿姆内特
and meet Amunet before midnight.
然后在交易完成前取消它
And call off the whole deal before it ever even happens.
对
Right.
你们说啥子呢
Angala what now?
要是他不早点消停
If he doesn't stop soon,
我就要申请提前被出售出去了
I'm gonna ask to be sold early.
当个超能力囚犯和超能力宠物
Being a meta-prisoner or a meta-pet--
有什么区别
what's the difference?
区别是阿姆内特·布莱克
Difference is Amunet Black.
她抓住超能力者
She captures metas,
把他们卖给出价最高的买主
sells them to the highest bidder.
黑手党老大  毒贩  黑道团伙
Mob bosses, drug traffickers, gangs--
想想我们的超能力会被用到糟糕的地方
just imagine how our powers could be used in the wrong hands.
我不当别人手里的枪
I ain't gonna be nobody's weapon.
我们得离开这
We gotta get outta here.
同意  但是怎么做
Agreed, but how?
沃夫和阿姆内特最近的犯罪行动
Wolfe and Amunet's latest criminal undertaking
恼人地打乱了我们的计划
throws an annoying wrench in our plans.
我们要怎么做
What shall we do?
我不知道
I don't know.
你
You,
你不知道
you don't know?
近乎无限的变量之网
My mind is consumed
已经穷尽了我的脑力
by a near infinite web of variables,
它们比一个正在爆炸的行星上的原子还多
more plentiful than there are atoms in an exploding star,
就目前来说  我不知道要怎么做
so for the moment, I do not know.
我不觉得这有什么好笑的
I fail to see the humor in this.
我听到  在你的大脑里
I heard that in your mind
一道神经信号闪电般的
a flash of stimuli racing through
传递到你的额前叶
your ventromedial prefrontal cortex,
在那里形成信仰
where belief is formed...
和疑虑
and doubt.
我没有一点儿疑虑
I don't have any doubt.
如果你不读我的心而是直接问我
And if you had asked, instead of reading my mind,
你就会知道
then you would know.
我确实知道
I do know.
至于说你之前的问题
As for your earlier inquiry,
关键不是我们要做什么
it's not about what we are going to do.
而是巴里·艾伦要做什么
It's about what Barry Allen is going to do.
等等  我快完事了
Hold your horses, almost done.
看起来像是一大堆头发堵住了存水弯
Looks like the trap got clogged with a bunch of hair.
我得到下面去一趟  确保堵塞被疏通
I'll head underneath, make sure the stack is clear.
我得走了
Good to go.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在如何
Okay, how's this?
出现在2017版的《小丑回魂》里
你知道《小丑回魂》里的那幅画吗
You know that painting in "It,"
活过来的那幅吗
the one that comes to life?
你看起来就跟它一样
It's like that.
我不可能做到
This is impossible.
我们不如把巴里打包
We might as well just gift wrap Barry,
交给阿姆内特  然后结束这一切
hand him to Amunet, and call it a day.
不  拉尔夫  这不是不可能的
No, Ralph, this is not impossible.
你的聚合细胞和你的意识息息相关
Your polymerized cells are linked to your thoughts.
你应当想变成谁就能变成谁才对
You should be able to change into anyone you can think of,
就像你把你的肚腩压缩成腹肌一样
just like when you squeezed your belly into abs.
好吧  首先
Okay, uh, first off,
我现在有在健身  这些肌肉是纯天然的
I have been working out, so this is au naturel now.
其次  那只是一些腹肌
And second, that was just some abs.
这是一整个人
This is an entire person.
我刚学会用震波的时候
when I first learned how to vibe,
我得学会怎么清空大脑
I had to learn how to clear my mind
里面的杂念
of all other thoughts.
你觉得你做得到吗
You think you can do that?
好吧  我会试试
all right, I'll try.
不止是要试试
Do better than try.
巴里的性命掌握在你手里
Barry's life is in your hands,
我们都指望着你
and we're all counting on you.
我觉得你想说的是
I think what you meant to say was,
"别有压力  小拉夫"
"No pressure, Ralphy."
-开始  -集中注意力
- Here we go. - All right, focus.
变成沃夫
Be Wolfe.
变沃夫  又大又坏的沃夫
Be Wolfe. Big, bad Wolfe.
看这漂亮的轮廓分明的颧骨  我成功了
Oh, wow, sweet, chiseled cheekbones, I did it.
说不定我真能救巴里
Wow, maybe I can save Barry.
能帮个小忙吗
Uh, a little help?
接下来我们得接决他的行走能力问题
Next, we need to work on his motor skills.
干得好  男孩
Well done, boy.
另外  我要声明
And hey, for the record,
我早就计划做
I was already planning on making
你用的那个东西了
that stuff that you used, so...
当然  就在你的午餐托盘撬棍行动以后
Sure, right after your lunch tray crowbar method.
我们能接着谈越狱脱出计划吗
Can we continue on with the breaking and exiting, please?
你指望我们听从一个警察的指挥越狱
You want us to follow a cop on a prison break?
我在这不是警察  我是个囚犯
I'm not a cop in here. I'm a prisoner.
而且我不想让阿姆内特把我
And I'm not about to let Amunet turn me
变成一个奴隶打手  你想吗
into a weaponized slave, are you?
你说服我了  我们走吧
Okay, you convinced me, let's go.
我留下
I'm staying.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
因为我不想伤害其他人
Because I don't wanna hurt anyone else.
上次我出去的时候
Last time I was out there,
我差不多毁了整座城市
I almost destroyed the whole city.
没错  她可以留下来
Yeah, she can stay.
不  我们都得走
No, we're all leaving.
贝琪  如果阿姆内特卖了你
Becky, if Amunet sells you,
你的超能力会被用来伤害很多人
your powers will be used to hurt a lot of people.
唯一阻止它发生的方法就是跟我们一起逃
The only way to prevent that is to escape with us.
拜托你了  相信我
Please, trust me.
大团圆了
Yay, oy, big happy.
然后怎么办
Now what?
沃夫说这个地方
Wolfe said that this wing
是建在过去的监狱上面的
was built on top of the old prison.
我也听到管道工谈到
I also heard the plumber talking about
管道在我们下面
piping underneath us.
一旦我们离这个禁超能力区足够远
Once we're far enough away from the meta-wing,
我们就会恢复超能力
we'll get our powers back.
这就是我们获得自由的方式
That's how we get our freedom.
是我的错  小不点
Aw, my bad, tiny.
一旦我们出去了
Hey, as soon as we get out,
我就会给你偷一双崭新的周杰女鞋
I'll steal you a brand new pair of Timmy Choos.
是周仰杰女鞋  我穿六号鞋
It's Jimmy. I'm a size six.
你真贴心
You're so sweet.
如果你想用你的超能力干点有用的事
If you wanna use your powers for something useful,
你可以帮我把一些土著工艺品偷回来
you could help me steal back some native artifacts.
如果你们俩准备接着犯罪
If you two plan on going back to crime,
那你们还是掉头回去吧
you might as well just turn around.
闪电侠会把你们俩逮回监狱的
The Flash will just run you back here.
你们其他人也一样
Same goes for all of you.
别看我  我洗心革面了
Don't look at me, I'm reformed.
从现在起  我只从事合法犯罪
From now on, I only commit legal crime.
合法犯罪
Legal crime?
股市
The stock market.
别聊了  我们还有好长一段路呢
Come on, we have a long way to go.
增幅完成
Augmentation is complete.
你的椅子可以使用了
Your chair will serve its purpose.
你又一次
You have outdone yourself
超越了你自己
once again.
我想要离开我的脑子里*
*Well, I think I'm going out of my head
你脑中的旋律
That melody in your head.
你没认出来
You don't recognize it?
我脑内播放的是
It was playing...
我们第一次跳舞时的配乐
The first time we danced, yes.
你还记得
So, you do remember?
1997年六月27日  下午一点
June 27th, 1997, 13 P.M.,
在波尔斯山下乡间的一个小村庄里
in the countryside in the small hamlet of Boars Hill.
那也是我们第一次接吻的地方
It was also the first time we kissed.
也是我第一次发觉
And the first time I realized
我想在你身边度过余生
I wanted to spend the rest of my life by your side.
马尔利泽
Marlize,
我什么都不会忘记
I forget nothing.
也许我们的歌曾经
Perhaps our song was once
在我意识中处于重要的位置
at the forefront of my consciousness,
但是现在
but now...
觉得自己要疯了*
*Think I'm going out of my head
你脑子里放的那首歌
That song playing in your head
让我很难读取你的思想
makes it difficult to read your thoughts.
非常困难
Quite difficult.
也许是故意的
Perhaps that's on purpose.
当然不是
Of course not.
我知道这意外的变化
I know this unforeseen change
让你担忧
concerns you.
但是别害怕
But fear not.
一旦这下个阶段完成
Once this next phase is complete,
我会扫除你脑内的所有疑问
I will erase every doubt from your head.
沃夫呼叫尖端科研实验室  我到了
Wolfe man to S.T.A.R. Base, I'm here.
拉尔夫  为了帮助你保持沃夫形态
Ralph, to help you stay as Wolfe,
我要给你接通到乔那里  好吗
I'm gonna hand you over to Joe, okay?
他会做你的后卫
He's gonna quarterback.
拉尔夫  收到了吗
Ralph, you copy?
收到
Yep.
那么  下一步要怎么办
So, what's the next move?
最好不要涉及到太多的移动
Preferably something without a lot of moving.
好  阿姆内特的核心手下是诺瓦克
Okay, Amunet's point man is Norvok,
所以你得先和他对话
so you're gonna have to talk to him first.
要杯喝的  表现的牛逼一点
Grab a drink, act like a hard-ass.
酒保
Barkeep,
来点冷冷冒白的  谢谢了
something cold and frosty, if you please.
天啊
Jeez.
这杯算你的  老兄
That's on you, bro.
脑袋里有蛇的来了  五点钟
Snake's on the brain, 5:00.
集中注意力  拉尔夫
Stay focused, Ralph,
别分心
no distracting thoughts.
加冰的金酒
Gingold on the rocks.
递给我  谢了
Hand it to me, please.
你在这里做什么
The hell you doing here?
我想和阿姆内特谈谈
I'd like to talk to Amunet,
谢谢  谈交易的事
please, about the deal.
你可以在交易的时候和阿姆内特谈
You could talk to Amunet at the deal.
该死的  拉尔夫
Damn it, Ralph,
没人敢那样对沃夫说话
nobody talks to Wolfe like that.
他是美国中西部最危险监狱的典狱长
He's the Warden of the most dangerous prison in the Midwest.
要他放尊重点
Demand some respect.
听着  你条宠物狗
Listen, you lapdog.
立刻安排我与你老板的会面
Set the meeting with your boss now,
不然我就拉出你的眼里的蛇
or I'll pull on your eye snake
然后用它勒死你  明白了吗
and strangle you with it, understood?
好了  好了
All right, all right.
我看看我能做些什么
Let me see what I can do.
天啊
Oh, God.
-怎样  -拉尔夫  你还好吗
- 'Sup? - Ralph, you okay?
挺好  没事
Yeah, fine, yeah.
没有一点问题
No problem here.
我可是牢牢的保持着呢
I'm definitely holding it together.
这听起来挺难让人相信的
Yeah, that doesn't sound too convincing.
一切都在我的掌控之下
I have complete control of the situation.
老德比是不会让朋友失望的
Ol' Dibny won't let his friends down.
沃夫
Wolfe.
阿姆内特准备好了
Amunet's ready.
那咱们就别让她等着了
Then let's not keep her waiting.
你确定这是正确的路吗
Are you sure this is the right way?
你听到下水道里的水声了吗
Do you hear the water in this sewer drain?
在向着这个方向走
It's moving in this direction.
我们继续朝这个方向前进
We keep going this way,
就是在远离监狱
we'll head away from the prison,
就能找到出口
find our exit.
观察细致
Wow, good catch.
你肯定是个特聪明的犯罪现场调查员
You must've been a really smart CSI.
这位调查员在自己的公寓里
A CSI who killed a teacher
杀了一个教师  还在各处留下了证据
in his own apartment and left evidence everywhere.
在我看来可不怎么聪明
Yeah, doesn't sound so smart to me.
说到这个  也许我们不该...
Hey, speaking of, maybe we shouldn't be...
该死
Crap.
慢着  慢着
Hey, easy, easy.
伦丁  慢着
Rundine, easy.
我们放了他  他会告发我们的
We let him go, he will out us.
-那我们就不能放了  对吗  -迪肯
- We can't do that, can we? - Deacon.
你在做什么  我们不能伤害他
What are you doing? No, we can't hurt him.
我们不能只弄伤他  我们没有选择
We have to do more than hurt him--we don't have a choice.
不行  我们不需要杀了他
No, hey, we do not have to kill him.
我们需要
Yes, we do.
不  我们不需要  好吗
No, we don't, all right?
把他绑起来就行
Just duct tape him.
快点  咱们走吧
Come on, let's move.
看起来很痛
Looked like it hurt.
叮叮
Ding, ding!
小伙子们  来吃点橙子片
Boys, have some orange slices.
妈妈要工作了  好吗
Mommy needs to work, okay?
典狱长
Warden...
我猜这不是那种
I'm going to assume this is not one
讲好事的紧急会面了
of those good emergency meetings--
还就在大型犯罪私下交易的几小时前
a few hours before a major criminal undertaking, hm?
我们要延后交易
We have to delay the deal.
什么
What?
我外边的耳目说警察被惊动了
My ears outside tell me the police have been tipped.
我不知道是怎么回事
I don't know how.
也许中城警局黑进了摄像头
Maybe CCPD hacked into the cameras.
你说那里没有摄像头
You said there were no cameras.
是吗
I did?
对  我是那么说过
Yes, I did say that.
但在那之后
But then, afterwards,
我安了几个
I installed a few.
是吗
Did you?
感觉你这个
something seems off
大坏沃夫有些不对劲啊
with the big, bad Wolfe,
如果你真是沃夫的话
if you even are Wolfe.
保持住  她在测试你
Stay in it, she's testing you.
你这是什么意思
What the hell's that supposed to mean?
我就是那个你一直在做交易的人
I'm the same man you've always dealt with.
好吧  那个人是谁呢
Okay, and who would that be?
给你货物的那个人
The one who gives you your merchandise.
相信我
And trust me,
你需要我多过我需要你
you need me a lot more than I need you.
所以  当我说交易要延后时
So, when I say the deal has to be delayed,
那就是因为交易需要延后
it's because the deal has to be delayed.
好吧
Okay.
怎么回事
What the hell?
什么
What?
你知道吗  有时候我真讨厌自己老是说对
You know, sometimes I hate being right all the time.
拉尔夫  快离开那里
Ralph, get out of there.
该死
Damn it.
给我找沃夫来
Get me Wolfe, yeah?
我理解你的担忧  阿姆内特
I understand your concern, Amunet,
但是我向你保证
but you have my word.
你的超能力者就在那里原封不动
Your metas are exactly where they're supposed to be--
锁在他们的监牢里
locked up tight and in their cells,
等着你来收他们
waiting for you to claim them.
很好  那我们到时候见
Very good, I'll see you then.
去找到他们
Find them!
我是说  肯定还有别的办法
I mean, there has to be another way.
没有别的办法了
There isn't.
还剩下一张牌可以打
There is one card left to play:
直接去铁山监狱
go to Iron Heights,
在交易进行前阻止他们
and stop the deal before it happens.
你这是要先找到阿姆内特
You're talking about finding Amunet,
在加上面对满监狱的武装超能力守卫
plus a prison full of armed meta-guards
协助他们
on their turf.
这是我们唯一的选择了
This is the only option we have left.
你们能做到的
You guys can do this.
我们走
Let's go.
拉尔夫
Ralph.
也许这次就不带我了吧
Yeah, uh, maybe not this time.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
你看  你...
Look, you--
你们不带我去救巴里
you're gonna have a better chance
成功几率会更高些
saving Barry without me.
拉尔夫  你知道不是这样的
Ralph, you know that isn't true.
我总是搞砸一切
I just screwed everything up.
你知道我再搞砸一次会怎么样吗
You know what could happen if I screw it up again?
-你不会的  -好吧  你知道吗
- You won't. - Okay, you know what?
也许我们只需要把这事谈清楚
Maybe we just need to talk this out,
咱们去走廊聊聊  来吧
let's go visit with Dr. Hallway, come on.
光谈话可修复不了我的脑袋
Look, bud, talk's not gonna fix my head.
这次我是不行了  各位
I just can't do it this time, guys.
抱歉让你们失望了
Sorry I let you down.
拉尔夫
Hey, Ralph.
看起来我们终于走到了旧监狱
Looks like we're finally in the old prison.
我们一定很接近了
We must be close.
比我们想的还近
Getting closer than we think.
我知道这锁
Hey, I know this lock.
这是和普通牢房一样的锁
It's the same kind they use in the general population wing,
也就是说在门的另一侧
which means there are no meta dampeners
没有超能力元电阻尼
on the other side of this door.
通过这扇门  就能重新获得超能力
We get through, we get our powers back.
这才是我想听到的
Well, that's all I needed to hear.
闪开
Out of the way.
满意啦
You good?
没脑子还没力气
No brains, no brawn.
让我试试
Allow me.
我是没有了超能力
I may not have my powers...
但我并不需要超能力来解决所有的问题
But I don't need them to hack my way out of trouble.
给我点时间
Give me a few minutes.
我看看
Come here.
什么  不  我没事
What, no, I'm fine,
一点都不疼
it doesn't really hurt.
你确定
Are you sure?
-看吧  -还是有点疼
- Yeah. - I mean, it hurts a little.
让我检查一下
Yeah, come here.
行了
There.
谢谢
Thanks.
看来我都忘了
Guess I forgot what it feels like
不用超能力打人是什么感觉
to punch someone in the face without my powers.
根据肿胀程度判断
Judging by the swelling,
应该是骨折  在第四或第五掌骨处
I'd say you have a fracture on either the fourth or fifth metacarpal.
-你怎么  -我以前经常跌倒
- How-- - I used to fall down a lot.
笨手笨脚
Super klutz.
你恢复自由后有什么打算
So, what are you gonna do when you're free?
我希望你不会走你的老路
I hope it's not more of what you did to get you in here.
不  相信我
Oh, no, trust me,
我已经受够了这里的囚服
I am so over prison jumpsuits.
橘色怎么穿都潮不起来
Orange is not the new anything.
灰色也是  所以
Neither is gray, neither is gray, so...
所以  然后呢
So, what then?
我也不知道
I don't know.
使用超能力只会伤害到周围的人
Using my powers just hurt those around me.
我的好运是别人的厄运
My good luck just jinxed everyone else.
你是真的关心身边的人
You know, you seem to really care about people--
不像那种会杀人的人
not like the type of person who'd take someone's life.
我没杀那个老师
I didn't kill that teacher.
我不会伤害任何人
I wouldn't take a life.
你要知道  并不是所有的超能力者
You know, not every meta
都会用超能力去伤害别人
uses their powers to hurt people.
有些选择去帮助别人
Some use them to help others,
保护他人
to protect people.
超能力并不能决定我们的本性
Our powers don't decide who we are.
只有我们自己能决定
We do.
拉尔夫
Ralph?
拉尔夫  你在里面吗
Hey, Ralph, you in here?
太亮了
Ick, the light!
刺眼
It burns!
行了  快点  该起床了
All right, come on, time to get up.
不行  我已经死了
I can't, I'm dead.
好吧  我不知道你是怎么回事
Okay, I don't know what's going on with you,
但我敢打赌这和你在酒吧变形的原因
but I'm betting it has something to do with the reason
有一定的关系
you literally fell apart at the bar.
我告诉过西斯科  说教对我没用
I told Cisco that a talk from him's not gonna help.
因此  你来说教
So, a talk from you
也是在白费力气  凯特琳
is not gonna help either, Caitlin.
好吧
Okay.
等我换个人来说
I'll get somebody else.
你好啊  弹性人
Hello, Stretch.
他们现在都叫我伸缩人
They call me a man who elongates now.
他们应该叫你"可悲"
They should call you pathetic.
不就是搞砸了吗  有什么大不了的
So, you screwed up, get over it.
你真是个毒舌妇
You are a mean lady.
我只是在实话实说而已
I am just telling you what you need to hear.
是吗  那等你走了我是不会想你的
Yeah, well, I'm not gonna miss you when you leave.
走
Leave?
你就因为这个伤心的
Is that what this is about?
对啊
Well, yeah.
所有人最终都会离开我
Everybody leaves Ralph Dibny eventually,
规则就是这样的
that's how this whole thing works.
我搞砸一次  他们就抛弃了我
I screw up big time, and, tch, they take off.
这一次  要离开我的
This time, the people who are gonna leave
是我的朋友
are actually my friends.
他们是我长久以来的第一份友谊
They're the first ones that I've had in a really long time.
真是愚蠢
That's stupid.
我本来也没指望你能理解
Yeah, well, I wouldn't expect you to understand,
你绑架刺伤了身边的朋友
you kidnap and stab all your friends.
对啊  我是失望界的女王
Right, I'm the queen of letting these people down.
但是你知道吗  他们依旧不离不弃
But you know what? They're still here.
不论我如何令他们失望
No matter how much I disappoint them,
他们依旧向我伸出援手
they still show up for me.
我还真是不理解
I don't really understand it,
这可能就是你所谓的友谊吧
but I think that's part of this whole friends thing.
除非你做了比绑架刺伤他们还要严重的事
So, unless you do something worse than kidnap and stab them,
我觉得你不会被抛弃的
I think you're gonna be just fine.
你真这么认为
You really think so?
对
Yes, I do.
你别说  这些话说得还挺不错的
You know, that actually wasn't a bad pep talk.
下次就该你来说了
Well, it's your turn next time.
当我准备重出黑道的时候
If I ever decide to go full villain again,
你可得给我来个蹩脚的比心之谈
you can give me the lame heart to heart.
超级坏蛋
Full villain?
等会
Wait...
Wait.
我知道该怎么补救了
I know how to fix this.
我得去找个女生聊一个男人的事
I gotta see a girl about a guy.
谢谢你  冰霜奥普拉
Thank you, Frosty Oprah.
马上就好
Presto.
所有人的超能力都恢复了
Everyone's powers work?
是的
Yep.
我能感受到5里之内所有的电器
I can smell all the tech within five miles of here.
谢谢你  巴里  你救了我们
Thank you, Barry, you saved us.
干得不错  伙计
You did good, boy.
还不够好嘛  看来
Not good enough, it seems.
所有人退回到牢房
Everyone back inside,
我就饶你们一命
and you'll live to see another day.
我看这里唯一
I think the only one
需要饶命的人是你
who should be worried about surviving right now is you.
这里没有装甲兵
There's no cavalry.
没人能看到发生了什么
No one's gonna see what happened here.
就只有这些人在场了  沃夫
It's just you and us, Wolfe.
你们想要复仇
You want revenge?
可以理解
Understandable.
只有一个问题
Just one thing--
如果你们如此渴望复仇
if you're thirsty for vengeance,
不得先从报复闪电侠开始
you might wanna start with The Flash.
巴里·艾伦就是闪电侠
Barry Allen is The Flash--
那个害你们锒铛入狱的人
the same man who put you behind bars
同样会毫不犹豫得将你们再次缉拿归案
and who will, no doubt, recapture you after your escape.
这可能一直以来都是他的计划
That was probably his plan all along...
他说的都是真的
Is all that true?
我要将你粉碎
I'm gonna squash you so quick,
速度之快甚至感受不到疼痛
you won't even know what hit you.
不  不能太快
No, not quick.
让我们好好折磨他
Let's take our time.
闪电侠跪倒在地
The Flash on his knees.
看来正义还是存在的
Suppose there is justice, after all.
把他捏成跳蚤般大小
Let's see how fast he can run
看他还能跑多快
when he's the size of a flea.
住手
Stop!
Stop.
你在干什么  小矮子
What are you doing, runt?
决定自己的本性
Deciding who I am.
你不准伤害他
You're not gonna hurt him.
要么加入我们  要么滚蛋
Join us, or get out of the way.
我们无论如何也要把他带走
Either way, we're taking him.
有运气就试试看
Good luck with that.
警告过你了
Toldja.
把他们射伤
Shoot to wound.
死了就没有价值了
They're no good to me dead.
他们不太可能会死
They most certainly are not.
阿姆内特  你来早了
Amunet, you're early.
而你正如我所猜测的一样
And you are exactly as I suspected,
一个骗子
a liar,
很明显是在越级执行命令
who's obviously in way over his head.
但是没关系
But no matter,
我会收拾好你的烂摊子的
I will clean up your mess for you.
小子  靠边站
Step aside, boys.
老娘要大展身手了
Mommy needs to work.
你在开玩笑吗
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
又来这一套
Not again.
迪沃
DeVoe.
我的工资可不包括解决这些的
Oh, I don't pay me enough for this.
超能力失效了
Powers won't work.
我的也是
Mine neither.
他肯定用某种仪器屏蔽了我们
He must have blasted us with something.
你他妈是谁
Who the hell are you?
我是你们的命运
I am your destiny.
不
No!
救我
Help me.
太晚了  艾伦先生
Too late, Mr. Allen.
多么低调的身体
Oh, what an inconspicuous body.
这会很有用
This will be quite useful.
不够快  监狱长
Not so fast, Warden.
你拿不走我的身体
You won't take my body.
我不想要你的身体
I don't want your body.
我要的是你的命
I want your life.
再见了  艾伦先生
Good-bye for now, Mr. Allen.
怎么了
What happened?
迪沃
DeVoe.
派对结束了
Well, party's over.
咱们离开这鬼地方
Let's get the hell out of here.
我不走
I'm staying.
什么  巴里
What? Barry...
我愿意这么做
I was only willing to do this--
想要带大家越狱
try to break everybody out
只是因为沃夫要卖掉我们
because Wolfe was gonna sell us,
但现在不会了
but that's not gonna happen now.
我要留下来
I'm staying
直到你们找到让我出去的合法途径
till you find a way to get me out of here legally.
这是唯一让我真正自由的方法
It's the only way I'd ever really feel free,
你们知道的
you know that.
这可能是我们能救出你唯一机会
This could be our only chance to save you.
我们都得决定自己是谁
We all have to decide who we are.
这就是我
This is who I am.
发生越狱
Breakout in progress.
启动封锁
Engage lockdown.
X号越狱
Code X prison breach.
重复  发生越狱
Repeat, we have a Code X.
快  快  快
Move, move, move!
靠着墙
Get against the wall.
牢房安全
Cell block secure.
亨利·艾伦曾在此  巴里也在
新证据  霍尔顿女士
New evidence, Ms. Horton--
你告诉法庭
that's what you told this court
你有了新证据
had come into your possession,
但我没听到也没看到
only I haven't heard it or seen it,
情况也没发生任何变化
nor have the circumstances changed in any way
不足以说服我再审
that would convince me to move for a retrial.
所以除非你还有其他证据
So, unless you have something more to add,
此次上诉庭审就结束了
this appeal hearing is over.
我明白  法官大人  我真的明白
I understand, your honor, I do,
再等几分钟
if we could just wait a few more minutes,
我确信
I am sure that--
我已经等得够久了
I am tired of waiting.
你有新证据
Either you have something new to add,
还是没有
or you don't.
到底有没有
Which is it?
我们没有新证据  法官大人
We have nothing further, your honor.
那我宣布巴里·艾伦上诉驳
Then I hereby deem Barry Allen's appeal den--
等下
Wait.
迪沃
DeVoe?
不  不是迪沃
Nope, not DeVoe.
是拉尔夫
It's Ralph.
我想你在找我
I believe you are looking for me,
法官大人
Your Honor.
我不知道这是怎么回事
I don't know how any of this happened.
你在巴里·艾伦的阁楼中被发现
You were found in Barry Allen's loft.
你已经死了
You were dead.
我被刺伤
I was stabbed.
我听到有人说什么
I heard a voice saying something about
陷害某人  然后我就晕倒了
framing someone, then I blacked out.
-会有用的  -今天早晨
- It's gonna work. - And this morning,
我在我家里醒来
I woke up in my own home.
迪沃夫人  你知道这些吗
Mrs. DeVoe, does any of this make any sense to you?
不
No,
我和你们一样
I am just as surprised
十分震惊
by all of this as everyone.
法官大人
Your Honor,
这个城市过去有报道
the city has had reports in the past
有些人看起来死了
of people who have appeared dead,
不料之后却发现还活着
only to later emerge very much alive.
不可能
That's impossible.
不可能  法官大人
Impossible, Your Honor,
这和
is it as impossible
人比声音跑得快
as a man who can run faster
一样不可能吗
than the speed of sound?
我认为中城
I submit that Central City is home
就是不可能的发源地
to the impossible.
我和你一样有很多问题  法官大人
I have as many questions as you have, Your Honor,
我期待和当局一起
and I am looking forward to working with the authorities
解决这一谜团
to solve this mystery.
我相信中城警局
Yes, I'm sure that CCPD
会对此十分感兴趣
will be very interested in this.
至于巴里·艾伦的上诉
As for Barry Allen's appeal...
我想法庭必须认为
I guess the court must deem that
克利福德·迪沃依旧活着
Clifford DeVoe is alive and well.
巴里·艾伦所有指控可以清除
Barry Allen is hereby cleared of all charges
即刻从铁山监狱
and ordered release from
释放
Iron Heights Penitentiary immediately.
你回家了
You're home.
你就是我的家
You're my home.
他等不及了
Oh, he couldn't wait to do that.
你感觉如何  巴里  还好吗
How you feeling, Barry, you okay?
我感觉很好
I'm feeling great, yeah.
看起来你得好好吃一顿
Well, you look like you could use a good meal,
别担心  我刚做了好多
and don't you worry, I made a fresh batch
埃丝特祖母的肉糕
of Grandma Esther's meat loaf.
-不错  -你喜欢我好开心
- Oh, yeah. - Just like you like it.
肉糕  好恶心
Meat loaf? Gross.
我的意思是  肉糕
I just meant, meat loaf is
在大多数餐厅
a grossly undervalued menu item
是非常不受欢迎的菜单项
in most restaurants, I think.
各位
You guys,
现在我自由啦  我不在乎做什么
now that I'm free, I don't care what I do.
能再和你们在一起我很开心
I'm just so happy to be back with all of you again.
闪电侠小组
Team Flash.
今天  我们为巴里庆祝
Today, we celebrate Barry.
明天我们继续
Tomorrow, we go back to stopping
阻止那个陷害你的人
the man that framed you.
我干了
I'll drink to that.
干杯  干杯
Here, here.
你还好吗  巴里
You okay, Barry?
只是迪沃
Yeah, it's DeVoe.
巴里  我们会阻止他  我们会的
Barry, we're gonna stop him, I know we will.
不  不是因为这个  他
No, that's not it, he...
没有东西阻止他
There was nothing keeping him
进入超能力片区中
from going inside the meta-wing
吸收铁山监狱里
and absorbing the powers
每个超能力者的超能力
of every meta in Iron Heights--
顶级藏猫猫的天气巫师
peek-a-boo top weather wizard.
没错  他本可以偷取他们更多的超力能
Yeah, I mean, he could've stolen their powers and more,
但他没有
but he didn't.
他只想要公交车上的超能力者
He only wants the bus metas.
他想要他们的超能力  所有那些人
He wants their powers for something--
为了什么
all of them.
我们认识一个公交车上的超能力者
We know a bus meta.
各位
Hey, guys.
不好意思我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
左边的臀肌
Just couldn't get this left glute
一直变不回之前那正常又自信的
to shape shift back to its normal, perky...
为什么都像看死人那样看着我
Why is everyone looking at me like I'm a dead man?
怎么了
What's all this?
昨晚成功之后
Well, after last night's success,
喝杯酒再合适不过了
I thought a toast was in order.
成功
Success?
你就是这么看待昨晚的
Is that what you call last night?
不错  你怎么认为
Yes, how would you describe it?
巴里·艾伦
Barry Allen was...
应该待在铁山监狱的超能力者片区
supposed to remain in the meta-human wing
但他现在出狱了
at Iron Heights, but he's now free.
即使是闪电侠小组有时也会幸运
Even Team Flash has good luck sometimes.
公交车超能力者呢
And the bus metas?
我们本应该等到
We were supposed to wait
所有的都被抓到
till all of them were captured.
但你只抓到四个
But you only got four.
我说的是我会从监禁中找到他们
I said I would retrieve them from confinement.
我从没说过何时何地
I never said when or where.
你还想着其他事情呢
There is something else on your mind,
对吗
isn't there?
沃夫监狱长的死
Warden Wolfe's death.
他必须死
He needed to die.
我只是不记得这对我们的计划是必要的
I just don't recall it being necessary for our plan.
椅子可以等到早上
The chair can wait till morning.
现在  敬智慧
For now, to the enlightenment.
敬智慧
To the enlightenment.
我爱你  克利福德
I love you, Clifford.
是的  我也爱你
Yes, and I, you.
我想我要疯了*
*I think I'm going out of my head
*Yes, I think I'm going out of my head
因为我不能解释我为何流泪*
*'Cause I can't explain the tears that I shed
为了你*
*Over you